Survival is the only victory.
Beast of War is a thriller, horror, war film directed by Kiah Roache-Turner.
When their boat sinks while crossing the Timor Sea during World War II, a troop of young
Australian soldiers must find a way to survive the harsh seas on a quickly shrinking raft.
Hundreds of miles from anywhere, they must confront interpersonal conflicts, enemy
attacks, and the advances of one very large, very hungry great white shark.
Leo, played by Mark Coles Smith.
Will, played by Joel Nankervis.
Des Kelly, played by Sam Delich.
Stan, played by Maximillian Johnson.
Teddy, played by Lee Tiger Halley.
Thompson, played by Sam Parsonson.
(German: Kein Tier.
So Wild.) is a 2025 film written, directed by Burhan Qurbani.
The film loosely based on William Shakespeare's play The Tragedy of Richard the Third, relocates its action to present-day Berlin, where
after a bloody gang war, Rashida, the youngest daughter of the Yorks, rises to become the leader of the Berlin underworld.
A European co-production, the film had its premiere at the 75th Berlin
International Film Festival in Berlinale Special section on 14 February 2025.
It will be released on 8 May 2025 in the German theaters.
The film explores themes of world war ii, based on true story,
survival, great white shark, survival horror.
The tone is dark and intense.